Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part One
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Files, 1710-1955; 21.07; (65 boxes)
  - Louise Caroline Alberta, Princess, Duchess of Argyll, 1848-1939, 1875-1900 (Box 39, Folder 1374)
  - Louise Victoria Alexandra Dagmar, Princess Royal of Great Britain and Duchess of Fife, 1867-1931, undated (Box 39, Folder 1375)
  - Love, Mabel, b. 1874, 1896-1902 (Box 39, Folder 1376)
  - Lover, Samuel, 1797-1868, undated (Box 39, Folder 1377)
  - Lowther, James, 1840-1904, 1887, undated (Box 39, Folder 1378)
  - Lubbock, John, Sir, 1834-1913, 1874-1901 (Box 39, Folder 1379-1380)
  - Lucy, Henry William, Sir, 1845-1924, 1892-1916, undated (Box 39, Folder 1381)
  - Lumley, Benjamin, 1811-1875, 1839-63 (Box 39, Folder 1382)
  - Lunn, Joseph, 1784-1863, 1854 (Box 39, Folder 1383)
  - Lush, Elizabeth Ann (Woollacot), d. 1881, 1880 (Box 39, Folder 1384)
  - Lush, Robert, 1807-1881, 1867 (Box 39, Folder 1385)
  - Lyceum Theatre, 1886 (Box 39, Folder 1386)
  - Lyell, Charles, Sir, 1797-1875, undated (Box 39, Folder 1387)
  - Lyndhurst, John Singleton Copley, Baron, 1772-1863, 1829-61, undated (Box 39, Folder 1388)
  - Lyttelton, Sarah Spencer Lyttelton, Baroness, 1787-1870, undated (Box 39, Folder 1389)
  - Lytton, Edith Villiers Bulwer-Lytton, Countess, 1841-1936, 1909, undated (Box 39, Folder 1390)
  - Lytton, Edward Bulwer Lytton, Baron, 1803-1873, undated (Box 39, Folder 1391)
  - Lytton, Edward Robert Bulwer Lytton, Earl of, 1831-1891, 1880-87 (Box 39, Folder 1392)
  - Macaulay, J. B., undated (Box 40, Folder 1393)
  - Macaulay, Thomas Babington Macaulay, Baron, 1800-1859, 1832-47 (Box 40, Folder 1394)
  - Macdermott, Gilbert Hastings, 1845-1901, 1874 (Box 40, Folder 1395)
  - Macdona, John Cumming, 1836-1907, 1901-05 (Box 40, Folder 1396)
  - Macdonnell, George, d. 1870, 1853 (Box 40, Folder 1397)
  - Macfarren, G. A. (George Alexander), Sir, 1813-1887, 1886, undated (Box 40, Folder 1398)
  - MacFarren, Walter Cecil, 1826-1905, 1867 (Box 40, Folder 1399)
  - Mackay, Charles, 1814-1889, 1861 (Box 40, Folder 1400)
  - Mackay, Mary, 1855-1924
    See: Corelli, Marie, 1855-1924, box 18, folder 622
  - Mackenzie, Compton, Sir, 1883-1972, 1915 (Box 40, Folder 1401)
  - Mackenzie, Morell, Sir, 1837-1892, 1884, undated (Box 40, Folder 1402)
  - MacKinlay, Antoinette (Sterling), 1843-1904, undated (Box 40, Folder 1403)
  - Macklin, F. H., 1895 (Box 40, Folder 1404)
  - Maclise, Daniel, 1806-1870, undated (Box 40, Folder 1405)
  - Macnaghten, W.H. (William Hay), Sir, 1793-1841, 1838 (Box 40, Folder 1406)
  - Macready, William Charles, 1793-1873, 1847-63, undated (Box 40, Folder 1407)
  - MacWhirter, John, 1839-1911, undated (Box 40, Folder 1408)
  - Magrath, John Richard, 1839-1930, 1881 (Box 40, Folder 1409)
  - Malet, Edward, Sir, 1837-1908, 1884 (Box 40, Folder 1410)
  - Malet, Lucas, 1852-1931
    See: Harrison, Mary St. Leger Kingsley, 1852-1931,box 31, folder 1149
  - Mallet, Bernard, Sir, 1859-1932, 1910-13 (Box 40, Folder 1411)
  - Mallet, Louis du Pan, Sir, 1864-1936, 1896 (Box 40, Folder 1412)
  - Malmesbury, James Howard Harris, Earl of, 1807-1889, 1857-87, undated (Box 40, Folder 1413)
  - Maltby, C.A. (C. Alfred), d. 1901, undated (Box 40, Folder 1414)
  - Manchester, Consuelo (Del Valle) Montagu, Duchess of, d. 1909, undated (Box 40, Folder 1415)
  - Manchester, Henry Montagu, Earl of, 1563?-1642, 1635 (Box 40, Folder 1416)
  - Manchester, William Drogo Montagu, Duke of, 1823-1890, 1853-89, undated (Box 40, Folder 1417)
  - Manning, Ambrose, 1897 (Box 40, Folder 1418)
  - Manns, August, Sir, 1825-1907, 1885-98, undated (Box 40, Folder 1419)
  - Mansel, Henry Longueville, 1820-1871, 1860-71 (Box 40, Folder 1420)
  - Mansfield, Howard, 1849-1938, 1908-26 (Box 40, Folder 1421)
  - Mansfield, James, Sir, 1733-1821, 1794, undated (Box 40, Folder 1422)
  - Mansfield, William Murray, Earl of, 1705-1793, undated (Box 40, Folder 1423)
  - Manvers, Sydney William Herbert Pierrepont, Earl, 1825-1900, 1853-66 (Box 40, Folder 1424)
  - Marks, Henry Stacy, 1829-1898, 1895 (Box 40, Folder 1425)
  - Marlborough, Frances Anne Emily (Vane) Spencer-Churchill, Duchess of, 1822- 1899, 1879-94, undated (Box 40, Folder 1426)
  - Marlborough, George Charles Spencer-Churchill, Duke of, 1844-1892, 1884 (Box 40, Folder 1427)
  - Marlborough, John Winston Spencer Churchill, Duke of, 1822-1883, 1866-76, undated (Box 40, Folder 1428)
  - Marlborough, Lilian Warren Hammersley Spencer-Churchill, Duchess of, d. 1907, 1888-96 (Box 40, Folder 1429)
  - Marlowe, Julia, 1865-1950, 1901 (Box 40, Folder 1430-1433)
  - Marryat, Frederick, 1792-1848, 1828 (Box 40, Folder 1434)
  - Marsh, Catherine, 1818-1912, undated (Box 40, Folder 1435)
  - Marshall, Polly, undated (Box 40, Folder 1436)
  - Marshall, Robert, 1863-1910, 1900-07 (Box 40, Folder 1437)
  - Marston, Henry & Georgina, undated (Box 40, Folder 1438)
  - Martin, George William, 1828-1881, 1867-69 (Box 41, Folder 1439)
  - Martin, Theodore, Sir, 1816-1909, 1879-1901, undated (Box 41, Folder 1440)
  - Martin, William, Sir, Bart., 1801-1895, 1840-48, undated (Box 41, Folder 1441)
  - Martin-Harvey, John, Sir, 1863-1944, 1900-19, undated (Box 41, Folder 1442)
  - Martineau, Harriet, 1802-1876, 1843, undated (Box 41, Folder 1443)
  - Marwood, William, 1820-1883, 1882, undated (Box 41, Folder 1444)
  - Mary, Princess, Duchess of Gloucester, 1776-1857, undated (Box 41, Folder 1445)
  - Mary, Queen, Consort of George V, King of Great Britain, 1867-1953, 1896, undated (Box 41, Folder 1446)
  - Mary Victoria Alexandra Alice, Princess Royal, Countess of Harewood, 1897-1966, 1897-1935 (Box 41, Folder 1447)
  - Marzials, Theodore, b. 1850, 1879-95 (Box 41, Folder 1448)
  - Maskelyne, John Nevil, 1839-1917, undated (Box 41, Folder 1449)
  - Mason, Arthur James, 1851-1928, 1884-1906 (Box 41, Folder 1450)
  - Massie, J. W. (James William), 1799- 1869, 1858 (Box 41, Folder 1451)
  - Mathews, Charles, 1776-1835, undated (Box 41, Folder 1452)
  - Mathews, Charles James, 1803-1878, 1850-76, undated (Box 41, Folder 1453)
  - Mathews, Helen, 1884 (Box 41, Folder 1454)
  - Matthew, J. E., 1897 (Box 41, Folder 1455)
  - Matthews, Amelia H., undated (Box 41, Folder 1456)
  - Matthews, Frank, 1843, undated (Box 41, Folder 1457)
  - Maud Charlotte Mary Victoria, Princess of Great Britain, Queen of Norway, Princess Charles of Denmark, 1869-1938, undated (Box 41, Folder 1458)
  - Maude, C. H., 1875 (Box 41, Folder 1459)
  - Maude, Cyril, 1862-1951, undated (Box 41, Folder 1460)
  - Mauly, Henry A., 1882 (Box 41, Folder 1461)
  - Max-Müller, Friedrich, 1823-1900, 1888 (Box 41, Folder 1462)
  - Maxwell, Mary Elizabeth Braddon, Mrs., 1837-1915, undated (Box 41, Folder 1463)
  - May, Thomas Erskine, 1815-1886, 1878-86, undated (Box 41, Folder 1464)
  - Mayne, Richard, 1796-1868, 1866-68, undated (Box 41, Folder 1465)
  - Mayo, Arabella (Praed) Bourke, Countess of, 1766-1843, 1840 (Box 41, Folder 1466)
  - Mayo, Blanche Julia (Wyndham) Bourke, Countess of, 1826-1918, undated (Box 41, Folder 1467)
  - Mayo, Richard Southwell Bourke, Earl of, 1822-1872, 1852-70, undated (Box 41, Folder 1468)
  - Melbourne, William Lamb, Viscount, 1779-1848, 1811-41 (Box 41, Folder 1469-1470)
  - Mellon, Alfred, 1820-1867, undated (Box 41, Folder 1471)
  - Mellon, Henry, undated (Box 41, Folder 1472)
  - Mellon, Harriot, 1777?-1837, 1832 (Box 41, Folder 1473)
  - Menken, Adah Isaacs, 1835-1868, undated (Box 41, Folder 1474)
  - Meredith, Madeleine, 1896 (Box 41, Folder 1475)
  - Meredith, Herman, 1806-1874, 1865-71, undated (Box 41, Folder 1476)
  - Metcalfe, Cranstoun, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 1477)
  - Michalawitz, Dr., 1837 (Box 42, Folder 1478)
  - Middlemass, Jean, 1834-1919, undated (Box 42, Folder 1479)
  - Midleton, William St. John Fremantle Brodrick, Earl of, 1856-1942, 1882-1900, undated (Box 42, Folder 1480)
  - Milford Haven, Louis Alexander Mountbatten, Marquis of, 1854-1921, 1891, undated (Box 42, Folder 1481)
  - Milford Haven, Victoria Alberta Elizabeth Mathilde Marie, Marchioness of, 1863-1950, 1894 (Box 42, Folder 1482)
  - Millais, John Everett, Sir, 1829-1896, undated (Box 42, Folder 1483)
  - Millard, Evelyn, 1875-1941, 1898, undated (Box 42, Folder 1484)
  - Millett, Maude, b. 1867, undated (Box 42, Folder 1485)
  - Millward, Jessie, b. 1861, undated (Box 42, Folder 1486)
  - Milman, Henry Hart, 1791-1868, 1843-61, undated (Box 42, Folder 1487)
  - Milner, Alfred Milner, Viscount, 1854- 1925, 1894-1901, undated (Box 42, Folder 1488)
  - Milner, Mr., undated (Box 42, Folder 1489)
  - Mitchell, 1806-1874, undated (Box 42, Folder 1490)
  - Molesworth, William, Sir, 1810-1855, 1847-54, undated (Box 42, Folder 1491)
  - Moller, Johannes, 1852 (Box 42, Folder 1492)
  - Monckton, Maria Louisa (Long), Lady, 1891, undated (Box 42, Folder 1493)
  - Moncrieff, Marri, undated (Box 42, Folder 1494)
  - Monk Bretton, John George Dodson, Baron, 1825-1897, 1875 (Box 42, Folder 1495)
  - Monkhouse, Harry, b. 1854, 1878 (Box 42, Folder 1496)
  - Monkswell, Robert Porrett Collier, Baron, 1817-1886, 1860-68 (Box 42, Folder 1497)
  - Montague, Henry James, 1843?-1878, 1834 (Box 42, Folder 1498)
  - Monteagle, Thomas Spring Rice, Baron, 1790-1866, 1865, undated (Box 42, Folder 1499)
  - Montefiore, Moses, Sir, 1784-1885, 1884 (Box 42, Folder 1500)
  - Monypenny, William Flavelle, 1866-1912, 1905-11, undated (Box 42, Folder 1501)
  - Moore, Eleanora, d. 1869, 1866, undated (Box 42, Folder 1502)
  - Moore, Eva, 1870-1955, 1901, undated (Box 42, Folder 1503)
  - Moore, Jessie, undated (Box 42, Folder 1504)
  - Morley, Samuel, 1809-1886, 1837-84, undated (Box 42, Folder 1505)
  - Morley, John, 1838-1923, 1880-1900 (Box 42, Folder 1506)
  - Morrell, H.H., undated (Box 42, Folder 1507)
  - Morris, Mowbray, undated (Box 42, Folder 1508)
  - Mortimer, J., 1874-79 (Box 42, Folder 1509)
  - Morton, Charles, d. 1904, 1882 (Box 42, Folder 1510)
  - Morton, John Maddison, 1811-1891, undated (Box 42, Folder 1511)
  - Motley, John Lothrop, 1814-1877, 1868 (Box 42, Folder 1512)
  - Mount Edgcumbe, Ernest Augustus Edgcumbe, Earl of, 1797-1861, 1855 (Box 42, Folder 1513)
  - Mount Edgcumbe, William Henry Edgcumbe, Earl of, 1833-1917, 1860-1911, undated (Box 42, Folder 1514)
  - Mountain, Mrs. Rossman (Wilkinson), 1768?-1841, 1831 (Box 42, Folder 1515)
  - Mowatt, Francis, Sir, 1837-1919, undated (Box 42, Folder 1516)
  - Mowbray, John, Sir, Bart., 1815-1899, 1877-90, undated (Box 42, Folder 1517)
  - Mozley, J. B. (James Bowling), 1813- 1878, undated (Box 42, Folder 1518)
  - Muncaster, Gamel Augustus Pennington, Baron, 1831-1862, 1861 (Box 42, Folder 1519)
  - Muncaster, Josslyn Francis Pennington, Baron, 1834-1917, 1872 (Box 42, Folder 1520)
  - Mundella, Anthony John, 1825-1897, 1867-96, undated (Box 42, Folder 1521)
  - Munster, George Augustus Frederick Fitzclarence, Earl of, 1794-1842, 1830 (Box 42, Folder 1522)
  - Murchison, Roderick Impey, Sir, 1792- 1871, undated (Box 43, Folder 1523)
  - Murray, Charles Augustus, Sir, 1806- 1895, 1839, undated (Box 43, Folder 1524)
  - Murray, Edward, undated (Box 43, Folder 1525)
  - Murray, John, 1808-1892, 1847-73, undated (Box 43, Folder 1526)
  - Murray, Julia, 1863 (Box 43, Folder 1527)
  - Murray, Malcolm, Sir, undated (Box 43, Folder 1528)
  - Murray, William H. (William Henry), 1790-1852, 1831-34 (Box 43, Folder 1529)
  - Musurus Pasha, Constantine, 1807-1891, 1860, undated (Box 43, Folder 1530)
  - Nachèz, Tivadar, 1859-1930, 1895, undated (Box 43, Folder 1531)
  - Naftel, Paul J. (Paul Jacob), 1817- 1891, 1886, undated (Box 43, Folder 1532)
  - Naish, J. G., 1824-1905, undated (Box 43, Folder 1533)
  - Nares, George S. (George Strong), 1831-1915, 1876 (Box 43, Folder 1534)
  - Nash, Joseph, 1809-1878, 1858 (Box 43, Folder 1535)
  - Nattate, Benjamin, undated (Box 43, Folder 1536)
  - Neeld, Joseph, 1789-1856, 1850-55 (Box 43, Folder 1537)
  - Neilson, Julia (Mrs. Fred Terry), 1868-1957, undated (Box 43, Folder 1538)
  - Neilson, Lilian Adelaide, 1848-1880, 1878, undated (Box 43, Folder 1539)
  - Nelson, Frances Elizabeth (Eyre) Nelson, Duchess, 1796-1878, undated (Box 43, Folder 1540)
  - Nelson, Horatio Nelson, Earl, 1823- 1913, 1879-1903, undated (Box 43, Folder 1541)
  - Nelson, Thomas, 1822-1892, 1857 (Box 43, Folder 1542)
  - Nesbit, E. (Edith), 1858-1924, undated (Box 43, Folder 1543)
  - Nettleship, Richard Lewis, 1846-1892, undated (Box 43, Folder 1544)
  - Nevill, H., undated (Box 43, Folder 1545)
  - Neville, Dorothy (Walpole), Lady, 1826-1913, undated (Box 43, Folder 1546)
  - Neville, G. F., 1874 (Box 43, Folder 1547)
  - Neville, Henry, 1837-1910, 1884-1903, undated (Box 43, Folder 1548)
  - Neville, Juliette, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 1549)
  - Newbould, William Williamson, 1819- 1886, undated (Box 43, Folder 1550)
  - Newbury, Anne (Webb) Livingston, Countess of, 1762-1861, 1837-41 (Box 43, Folder 1551)
  - Newcastle, Henry Pelham Alexander Pelham-Clinton, Duke of, 1834-1879, 1865 (Box 43, Folder 1552)
  - Newcastle, Henry Pelham, 1864-1928, 1894-98 (Box 43, Folder 1553)
  - Newnes, George, 1851-1910, 1884-99, undated (Box 43, Folder 1554)
  - Newnham-Davis, Lieut.-Col. (Nathaniel), 1854-1917, undated (Box 43, Folder 1555)
  - Newton, Ann Mary (Severen), 1832-1866, 1862 (Box 43, Folder 1556)
  - Newton, C. T. (Charles Thomas), 1816- 1894, 1870-93 (Box 43, Folder 1557)
  - Nicholl, H. W. (Horace Wadham), 1848- 1922, 1883 (Box 43, Folder 1558)
  - Nicholl, John, 1790-1871, 1843-71 (Box 43, Folder 1559)
  - Nicholls, Agnes, 1900 (Box 43, Folder 1560)
  - Nichols, John Gough, 1806-1873, 1837-71, undated (Box 43, Folder 1561)
  - Nicol, J. Watson, 1901, undated (Box 43, Folder 1562)
  - Nicol, Mrs., d. 1834?, undated (Box 43, Folder 1563)
  - Nicolas, Nicholas Harris, Sir, 1799- 1848, 1822-46, undated (Box 43, Folder 1564)
  - Nisbett, Louisa Cranstoun, 1812?-1858, undated (Box 43, Folder 1565)
  - Noel, Roden Berkeley Wriothesley, 1834-1894, 1871, undated (Box 43, Folder 1566)
  - Norfolk, Lady Charlotte Sophia (Leveson-Gower) Howard, Duchess of, 1788-1870, 1842-53, undated (Box 44, Folder 1567)
  - Norfolk, Henry Charles Howard, Duke of, 1791-1856, 1836-52, undated (Box 44, Folder 1568)
  - Norfolk, Henry Granville Fitzalan- Howard, Duke of, 1815-1860, 1857, undated (Box 44, Folder 1569)
  - Norfolk, Henry Fitzalan-Howard, Duke of, 1847-1917, 1874-1915, undated (Box 44, Folder 1570)
  - Norman, Henry, 1858-1939, 1898 (Box 44, Folder 1571)
  - Normand, Henrietta Rae, 1859-1928, 1891, undated (Box 44, Folder 1572)
  - Normanton, James Charles Herbert Welbore Ellis Agar, Earl, 1818-1896, 1878-95 (Box 44, Folder 1573)
  - Norreys, Grace, undated (Box 44, Folder 1574)
  - North, John William, 1842-1924, 1896-1920 (Box 44, Folder 1575)
  - North, William Henry John North, Baron, 1836-1932, 1888 (Box 44, Folder 1576)
  - Northbrook, Thomas George Baring, Earl of, 1826-1904, 1866-93 (Box 44, Folder 1577)
  - Northcliffe, Alfred Harmsworth, Viscount, 1865-1922, 1910-18 (Box 44, Folder 1578)
  - Northcliffe, Mary Elizabeth Harmsworth, Viscountess, undated (Box 44, Folder 1579)
  - Northern Institute of Languages and Commerce, 1898 (Box 44, Folder 1580)
  - Northumberland, Algernon George Percy, Duke of, 1810-1899, 1871-85 (Box 44, Folder 1581)
  - Northumberland, Algernon Percy, Duke of, 1792-1865, 1848-65, undated (Box 44, Folder 1582)
  - Northumberland, Edith (Campbell) Percy, Duchess of, 1849-1913, 1889-91 (Box 44, Folder 1583)
  - Northumberland, Henry George Percy, Duke of, 1846-1918, 1885-1907, undated (Box 44, Folder 1584)
  - Northumberland, Hugh Percy, Duke of, 1785-1847, 1842 (Box 44, Folder 1585)
  - Norton, Caroline Sheridan, 1808-1877, undated (Box 44, Folder 1586)
  - Nugent, C., 1844 (Box 44, Folder 1587)
  - Oakes, John Wright, 1863 (Box 44, Folder 1588)
  - Oakeley, Octavius, undated (Box 44, Folder 1589)
  - Oakley, Kenneth Page, 1856 (Box 44, Folder 1590)
  - O'Connor, Arthur, 1763-1852, 1891 (Box 44, Folder 1591)
  - Oliveira, Benjamin, 1853-57 (Box 44, Folder 1592)
  - Oliver, Martha Cranmer, 1834-1880, undated (Box 44, Folder 1593)
  - Ollier, Charles, Jr., 1908 (Box 44, Folder 1594)
  - O'Mara, Joseph, b. 1866, undated (Box 44, Folder 1595)
  - O'Neil, Henry Nelson, 1817-1880, undated (Box 44, Folder 1596)
  - Onslow, William Hillier Onslow, Earl of, 1853-1911, 1907, undated (Box 44, Folder 1597)
  - Onslow, William Lake, 1820-1877, 1872 (Box 44, Folder 1598)
  - Oppenheim, E. Phillips (Edward Phillips), 1866-1946, 1915 (Box 44, Folder 1599)
  - Oppert, Gustav, 1871 (Box 44, Folder 1600)
  - Orchardson, Charles M. Q., b. 1873, undated (Box 44, Folder 1601)
  - Orchardson, William Quiller, Sir, 1832-1910, undated (Box 44, Folder 1602)
  - O'Rell, Max, 1848-1903, 1888-99 (Box 44, Folder 1603)
  - Orsini, Felice, 1819-1858, 1857 (Box 44, Folder 1604)
  - Orton, Arthur, 1834-1898, 1873 (Box 44, Folder 1605)
  - Osbaldeston, D. W., 1831-46, undated (Box 44, Folder 1606)
  - Osborne House, Isle of Wight, undated (Box 44, Folder 1607)
  - Osborne, George Alexander, 1806-1893, 1869 (Box 44, Folder 1608)
  - Ossington, Lady Charlotte (Bentinck) Denison Scott, Viscountess, 1806-1889, undated (Box 44, Folder 1609)
  - Ossington, John Evelyn Denison, Viscount, 1800-1873, 1859 (Box 44, Folder 1610)
  - Ottley, William Young, 1771-1836, 1830 (Box 45, Folder 1611)
  - Otway, Arthur (Arthur John), Sir, 1822-1912, undated (Box 45, Folder 1612)
  - Ouless, Walter William, 1848-1933, 1877-1924, undated (Box 45, Folder 1613)
  - Overall, William Henry, 1829-1898, 1876 (Box 45, Folder 1614)
  - Overstone, Samuel Jones Loyd, Baron, 1796-1883, 1865-76 (Box 45, Folder 1615)
  - Owen, Richard, 1804-1892, 1851 (Box 45, Folder 1616)
  - Oxenbridge, William John Monson, Viscount, 1829-1898, 1888 (Box 45, Folder 1617)
  - Oxenford, Edward, 1878-93 (Box 45, Folder 1618)
  - Oxenford, John, 1812-1877, undated (Box 45, Folder 1619)
  - Oxford University, Balliol College, Musical Society, 1889-97 (Box 45, Folder 1620)
  - Paget, Violet, 1856-1935
    See: Lee, Vernon, 1856-1935, box 38, folder 1332
  - Paget, Walter, 1863-1935, undated (Box 45, Folder 1621)
  - Pain, Amelia Lehmann, d. 1920, undated (Box 45, Folder 1622)
  - Pain, Barry, 1864-1928, 1895 (Box 45, Folder 1623)
  - Palgrave, Francis, Sir, 1788-1861, undated (Box 45, Folder 1624)
  - Palgrave, Reginald F. D. (Reginald Francis Douce), Sir, 1829-1904, 1866 (Box 45, Folder 1625)
  - Palk, Laurence V., Sir, Bart., 1793- 1860, 1847-48 (Box 45, Folder 1626)
  - Palmer, Elizabeth, 1874 (Box 45, Folder 1627)
  - Palmer, Millicent, 1867 (Box 45, Folder 1628)
  - Palmer, Sutton, 1854-1933, undated (Box 45, Folder 1629)
  - Palmer, William, 1824-1856, 1855-56 (Box 45, Folder 1630)
  - Palmerston, Emily Lamb, Viscountess, 1787-1869, 1855-65, undated (Box 45, Folder 1631)
  - Palmerston, Henry John Temple, 1784- 1865, 1811-60 (Box 45, Folder 1632)
  - Pardoe, Miss (Julia), 1806-1862, undated (Box 45, Folder 1633)
  - Parker, Henry Perlee, 1795-1873, undated (Box 45, Folder 1634)
  - Parker, John, 1830-1916, 1885 (Box 45, Folder 1635)
  - Parkes, Bessie Rayner, 1829-1925
    See: Belloc, Bessie Rayner, 1829- 1925, box 6, folder 206
  - Parry, John, undated (Box 45, Folder 1636)
  - Parry, John Orlando, 1810-1879, undated (Box 45, Folder 1637)
  - Parry, Thomas, Bp. of Barbados, 1795- 1870, 1856 (Box 45, Folder 1638)
  - Parsons, Alfred, 1847-1920, 1906 (Box 45, Folder 1639)
  - Pateman, Robert, b. 1841, 1884, undated (Box 46, Folder 1640)
  - Paterson, Arthur, 1862-1928, 1898 (Box 46, Folder 1641)
  - Patey, Janet Monach (Whytock), 1842- 1894, 1881 (Box 46, Folder 1642)
  - Patey, John George, 1842-1901, 1872 (Box 46, Folder 1643)
  - Paton, J. Noël, Sir, 1821-1901, 1872 (Box 46, Folder 1644)
  - Patten, George, 1801-1865, 1845 (Box 46, Folder 1645)
  - Patti, Adelina, 1843-1919, 1868-1900, undated (Box 46, Folder 1646)
  - Pauer, Ernest, 1826-1905, 1881-90 (Box 46, Folder 1647)
  - Paul, C. Kegan (Charles Kegan), 1828- 1902, 1882-84 (Box 46, Folder 1648)
  - Paul, Howard, 1835-1905, 1879, undated (Box 46, Folder 1649)
  - Paul, Isabelle Howard (Featherstone), 1833-1879, 1865-75 (Box 46, Folder 1650)
  - Paulton, Harry, 1842-1917, 1916 (Box 46, Folder 1651)
  - Paxton, Joseph, Sir, 1801-1865, undated (Box 46, Folder 1652)
  - Payne, Edmund, b. 1865, 1901 (Box 46, Folder 1653)
  - Payne, John Horne, 1837-1920, undated (Box 46, Folder 1654)
  - Payne, Joseph, 1797-1870, 1837 (Box 46, Folder 1655)
  - Payton, Charles Alfred, Sir, 1843-1926, 1895 (Box 46, Folder 1656)
  - Peabody, George, 1795-1869, 1866 (Box 46, Folder 1657)
  - Peacock, Ralph, 1868-1946, 1900 (Box 46, Folder 1658)
  - Peake, Richard Brinsley, 1792-1847, 1842 (Box 46, Folder 1659)
  - Pearson, Hesketh, 1887-1964, 1941-49 (Box 46, Folder 1660)
  - Pease, Joseph, 1799-1872, 1855 (Box 46, Folder 1661)
  - Pease, Joseph Whitwell, Sir, Bart., 1828-1903, 1866-81 (Box 46, Folder 1662)
  - Peel, Arthur Wellesley Peel, Viscount, 1829-1912, 1873-98, undated (Box 46, Folder 1663)
  - Peel, Charles Lennox, Sir, 1823-1899, 1876-96 (Box 46, Folder 1664)
  - Peel, James, 1811-1906, 1886, undated (Box 46, Folder 1665)
  - Peel, Jonathan, 1799-1879, 1866 (Box 46, Folder 1666)
  - Peel, Julia (Floyd), Lady, d. 1859, 1830 (Box 46, Folder 1667)
  - Peel, Robert, Sir, 1788-1850, 1827-43, undated (Box 46, Folder 1668)
  - Peel, Robert, Sir, Bart., 1822-1895, 1861 (Box 46, Folder 1669)
  - Pelham-Clinton, Edward William, Lord, 1836-1907, 1879 (Box 46, Folder 1670)
  - Pembroke, George Robert Charles Herbert, Earl of, 1850-1895, 1873-85, undated (Box 46, Folder 1671)
  - Pengelly, William, 1812-1894, undated (Box 47, Folder 1672)
  - Penley, William Sydney, 1852-1912, 1895-1911, undated (Box 47, Folder 1673)
  - Pennell, Elizabeth Robins, 1855-1936, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 1674)
  - Pennell, Joseph, 1857-1926, 1900-12 (Box 47, Folder 1675)
  - Perry, Helen, fl. 1810-1848, 1870 (Box 47, Folder 1676)
  - Petrie, Graham, 1859-1940, 1900 (Box 47, Folder 1677)
  - Petrie, Hilda Urlin, Lady, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 1678)
  - Petrie, W. M. Flinders (William Matthew Flinders), Sir, 1853-1942, 1883-1901 (Box 47, Folder 1679)
  - Pettie, John, 1839-1893, 1874-93, undated (Box 47, Folder 1680)
  - Pettigrew, Thomas Joseph, 1791-1865, 1838 (Box 47, Folder 1681)
  - Pettitt, Henry, 1848-1893, 1892, undated (Box 47, Folder 1682)
  - Phelps, Samuel, 1804-1878, 1860-75, undated (Box 47, Folder 1683)
  - Phene, J. S., 1872-79 (Box 47, Folder 1684)
  - Philipps, Thomas, 1777-1841, undated (Box 47, Folder 1685)
  - Phillimore, Robert, Sir, 1810-1885, 1850-81, undated (Box 47, Folder 1686)
  - Phillimore, W. P. W. (William Phillimore Watts), 1853-1913, 1894 (Box 47, Folder 1687)
  - Phillip, John, 1817-1867, 1865-66, undated (Box 47, Folder 1688)
  - Phillips, Claude, Sir, 1848-1924, 1907 (Box 47, Folder 1689)
  - Phillips, Henry, 1801-1876, 1847-54 (Box 47, Folder 1690)
  - Phillips, Henry Wyndham, 1820-1868, undated (Box 47, Folder 1691)
  - Phillips, J. Burton, undated (Box 47, Folder 1692)
  - Phillips, John, 1800-1874, undated (Box 47, Folder 1693)
  - Phillips, T. W., fl. 1821-1826, 1841 (Box 47, Folder 1694)
  - Phillips, Watts, 1825-1874, 1864-71, undated (Box 47, Folder 1695)
  - Philp, Elizabeth, 1827-1855, 1880, undated (Box 47, Folder 1696)
  - Philpott, Henry, Bp. of Worcester, 1807-1892, 1847 (Box 47, Folder 1697)
  - Phipps, Charles Beaumont, Sir, 1801- 1866, 1836-62, undated (Box 47, Folder 1698)
  - Phipps, Margaret Anne (Bathurst), Lady, d. 1874, 1857 (Box 47, Folder 1699)
  - Pickering, J. L., fl. 1872-1893, 1876 (Box 47, Folder 1700)
  - Pickering, William Alexander, 1840- 1907, 1897 (Box 47, Folder 1701)
  - Pickersgill, Frederick Richard, 1820- 1900, 1863-68, undated (Box 47, Folder 1702)
  - Pigott, Edward F. S., 1823-1895, 1869-79 (Box 47, Folder 1703)
  - Pirbright, Henry de Worms, Baron, 1840-1903, 1872-90 (Box 47, Folder 1704)